(Episode 2)
Eun Seo's father is
the president of the Parents Association.
Her brother is
the president of the Students' Union.
And Eun Seo is the class vice president.
The class president?
Hello.
Ms. Im Kyung Ha.
Sin Ae is the top student
in the whole school,
and the class vice president.
What?
Are you the vice president?
Mom.
Hello, I am Choi Sin Ae.
Sin Ae.
Hi.
You are pretty.
I don't want to take up your time
knowing that you are busy,
but since the parents
of class representatives are here,
I would love to discuss
school matters with you.
School matters?
I don't know anything about that.
I told you not to take any positions
such as a class vice president.
No, please don't worry.
I did not intend to cause any burden.
Ms. Kim Soon Im.
You must be very proud of her.
Her classmates voted for her.
So, you should let her take on her role.
Dad.
Jun Seo.
Excuse me. I need to go to the restroom.
All the students have worked
so hard on this exhibition.
Luckily all the classmates...
get along well,
following Eun Seo and Sin Ae's lead...
There's a call for you, teacher.
Okay.
Excuse me for a minute.
You must be delighted
that Sin Ae is good at school.
I am sure you are as well.
Sin Ae, do you have siblings?
She has an older brother.
Does she? Just like us.
What grade is he in?
He is supposed to be in high school.
He is preparing for the GED now.
- He was expelled.
- Hey, you!
I see.
Do you get along with your brother?
No.
Ms. Soon Im.
Has Sin Ae ever gotten sick
when she was little?
Look.
Although I don't have much to offer,
I take good care of my children.
It is none of your business.
My goodness.
Mom.
What is she like?
Who?
The girl who is the class president.
Yoon Eun Seo?
She is like a princess.
I heard her grandfather founded
this school.
Her family is very wealthy.
That annoys me.
Sin Ae's mother came to check out
the blood type of her daughter.
She has Type O blood.
Mom and Dad seem to be tired.
They don't want to come out.
Honey, are you tired?
Of course, I am. I went to the exhibition.
I think Eun Seo is making
something delicious,
and she would be disappointed.
She won't.
Eun Seo is a lovely, considerate girl.
So she would understand.
- Happy birthday.
- Thank you.
Open it. It's for you.
They are us, our family.
They are.
Eun Seo and I made them together.
No, Jun Seo made them and drew them.
He baked them in a kiln.
What did you do, then?
I was rooting for him.
We will be fine sending them away
as long as we have these mugs.
Why do we have to send them away?
I will live with them forever.
Of course, you will.
That is yours.
Why do we have to send them away?
I will live with them forever.
Of course, you will.
You're good at mimicking your mom.
I just sound like her
because I am her daughter.
Like mother, like daughter.
Jun Seo.
You always give me
the leftovers after selling food.
Do you want me to go on an empty stomach?
You said you don't want it.
Mom, what's wrong with you these days?
Why are you so grumpy?
Come home early.
If I come home early,
you will have me work for you.
That is why my brother ran away.
What? What did you say?
Sin Ae!
Come home early!
It is a market day.
There will be a lot of customers.
Eun Seo, here's your lunchbox.
What is today's menu?
It is pork cutlet, isn't it?
Thanks, Mom.
I am ready.
Eun Seo, wait. Your hair...
Are they thin?
They were thick before.
When did they become thinner?
I am probably not your daughter.
I don't even look like you.
You might have adopted me.
What?
I'll go without you if you don't hurry.
Eun Seo, you are good to go.
Mom, have a good day.
Wait for me.
Jun Seo, give me a ride on your bike.
What?
No, you're heavy.
Are you that lazy to not even
ride your bike?
Fine.
Why am I so tired?
I feel dizzy, too.
I feel like I might have another accident.
It is probably risky
since I'm not good at riding a bike.
Get on.
Thanks.
But only this time.
Also, don't say such a thing ever again.
Sorry.
It's lunchtime!
Eun Seo has
a scrumptious-looking lunchbox.
Come here, everyone.
- Come here.
- Open it.
It's like a flower garden!
Pork cutlets, grilled sausages,
and even rolled omelets.
Let's dig in. I will try them all.
It looks so delicious.
Let me try them, too.
- I'll get some water.
- Don't take too long.
I'm sorry, Sin Ae.
Sin Ae.
Choi Sin Ae.
You don't want...
your classmates to see us
while we're talking here.
Let me go.
I don't have any money. I really don't.
Don't be like that.
You are just like your mom.
I know you have sneaked money
from the restaurant.
So give it to me when I am nice.
Are you saying I am a thief?
You're the one who ran away taking money.
What? What did you just say?
Stop it.
Here, I have money.
Take this. You can take this.
Here you are.
Choi Sin Ae. Is she your friend?
What are you doing?
Who do you think you are?
You!
No!
Thanks.
Don't ever come back!
Is he your brother?
Yes, he is my brother.
He is a gangster.
Are you happy now?
No, I am not...
I really wish you would disappear.
Sin Ae.
Sin Ae, why were you crying?
The school is pretty far from your house,
can't you ride a bike?
No, I cannot.
Then, can I...
I cannot ride one,
because I don't have one.
We cannot afford a bike.
A bike is for kids like Eun Seo.
When did your dad pass away?
Before I was born.
Have you ever thought...
"I wish I had a father?"
I am sorry.
You are a good girl.
You help your mom, but you are still
at the top of the whole school.
She leaves me alone when I study.
I can't wait to grow up
to run away from home.
I am sorry.
How cute you are.
Is he a philanthropist?
Like father, like daughter.
Where can I find a father like him?
Why did you hit me?
Where did you get this?
Who gave it to you?
Tell me the truth.
I did not do anything wrong.
Eun Seo's father, whom we met before.
Why did you meet him?
We ran into each other near the school.
Are you a beggar?
- Are you a beggar?
- Mom.
Why did you get this from him?
Get out of here!
I am working like a dog
to feed you and let you study.
And now you are acting like...
Get out of here!
What is wrong with you?
Does it make you that upset
that I got a teddy bear?
What have you ever done for me?
Have you ever bought me
something like this?
All you do every day is beat me, scold me,
and force me to work at your restaurant.
What?
You're right.
Despite having so much money,
I never bought you a doll.
And I made you work in a restaurant,
so I can have a good life for myself.
Yes, I did just that!
I am sick of this.
No one lives like me.
Even if they are much worse
at school work,
they wear better clothes than me.
And they get this thing
as much as they want.
But, what about me?
Eun Seo, who is worse than I am at school,
is the president because of her parents.
What am I?
Go live with them
if you're so envious of that.
Go live with them.
Okay, I will go there.
I will get out of here.
Get out of my face.
Go live there because that is your house.
Go with your wealthy biological parents!
Biological parents?
Did you say, "biological parents?"
What do you mean?
What do you mean by that?
Your dreams have come true.
You are about to leave this house,
you ingrate.
Go to your wealthy parents.
Go to your wealthy biological parents
who can afford to buy this thing.
How come you are here?
When I was passing by on a bus...
I saw your car, so I got off.
Where were you coming from?
What about you?
I just...
Why don't we go somewhere with
Eun Seo and Jun Seo to get some fresh air?
Today?
Yes, let's go, please.
Yes.
Good job.
Roll it now.
Pull it a little.
Roll it again.
A little more.
Good. Pull it up...
Great job.
Good. Roll it.
That's right. Make it tight.
A little more.
Great.
Honey, aren't you cold?
Do you want me to bring your shawl?
Honey, you look good with Eun Seo.
The dean called this afternoon.
You were not there...
so I told him we would go
to be exchange professors as planned.
Honey, today, I am actually...
Honey, I am happy now.
We are happy now.
Please let it go. Please do it for me.
I will be a better wife.
I will be a better mom.
I can forget everything and move on
if we are like this.
So please do it for me.
Please.
Let me see.
It is working fine.
Don't you think you aren't good at it?
No, Eun Seo, you are prettier.
Whom do you look after to be so pretty?
I am pretty because I look like my mom.
Do you want to see her?
Okay.
Your mom is so beautiful.
Eun Seo, are you feeling good?
Yes, Eun Seo is in a good mood today.
It makes me the happiest dad.
It gives me the happiest feeling, too.
Yoon Jun Seo, are you feeling good?
I am so happy as well.
That was funny.
Sin Ae, what's wrong?
I was kicked out of my house.
I have nowhere to go.
Choi Sin Ae.
But why did you come here...
Is that...
My mom beat me
because of this teddy bear you bought me.
Sin Ae, I can come with you...
I heard everything.
My mom told me all about it.
Mom, what is this about?
Is that true?
Is it true I am your daughter?
Sin Ae.
- You and I were switched.
- Sin Ae.
I am their daughter, not you.
Eun Seo.
Yoon Eun Seo.
How did you come this far?
It is late at night, what if you get lost?
Am I really not their daughter?
Am I not your sister?
Yes, you are my sister.
You are my sister.
She said I am not.
Eun Seo.
Right, it did not feel right.
I am not good at paintings like you are.
Everyone says we don't look alike.
I am not good at school.
Mom, Dad, and you all are smart.
But I am not.
Yoon Eun Seo, that's enough.
You are my sister.
So, let's go home.
Yoon Eun Seo, let's go back.
Are you really doing this?
All right, then you are not my sister.
My sister is a good girl.
My sister is not a girl
who makes her brother upset.
Do you have any idea how scared I was
when you were gone?
Even when we play Hide-and-Seek,
my sister puts a mark
on a location she hides,
in case I take too much time to find her.
My sister is that kind of a girl.
That's her. That is my sister.
Why are you crying?
Let's go.
I'll give you a piggyback ride.
How are Jun Seo and Eun Seo?
How is Sin Ae?
Bring her back tomorrow morning.
- Honey.
- Bring her back.
How can we do that to her?
Why are you so cruel?
Yes, I am cruel.
If Eun Seo is your daughter,
Sin Ae is your daughter, too.
Sin Ae is our actual daughter.
Have you imagined
how her life has been for 14 years?
If she had had a good life...
if she had had a good life
like that of Eun Seo,
I wouldn't be doing this.
Thinking of her lived
in that soup restaurant until now...
And thinking of her
growing up in that house...
That's enough.
I can't. I can't send her back.
I won't do it.
Can you do that?
Don't you care about Sin Ae,
not even a little?
Caring for her...
I will not think about her.
Honey.
If I care for her, what about Eun Seo?
Have you thought about
how Eun Seo would feel?
Are you going to give her up?
Are you going to kick her out?
If I don't protect Eun Seo now, who would?
If I don't keep myself together,
we'll lose Eun Seo.
We will lose her forever.
Don't touch Eun Seo's clothes.
I got fresh underwear for you
to change into.
Take a seat, Eun Seo.
Good morning.
"The whole school will know soon."
Isn't that what you thought?
Eun Seo.
"How would she bear even a day?
I'm so worried."
Isn't that what you thought?
"She should stop going to school
for a while."
Isn't that what you thought?
"I will be strong despite all this."
You think, "I believe in Eun Seo." Right?
Yes, I believe in you.
So do I.
I won't be weak. Don't worry.
So, do you live in her house?
Of course,
It was my home from the beginning.
Then, she should go to your house.
She had better do it.
Eun Seo.
What a surprise.
Eun Seo, what are you supposed to do now?
What are you supposed to do, Eun Seo?
Stop crying, Kang Hee.
Stop crying. It is fine.
Welcome...
A bowl of hot soup with rice, please.
So she did go to your house.
What do we do now?
What are we supposed to do?
How do others deal with
this kind of matter?
Do they switch their children back?
Should we...
switch our children back as well?
Sin Ae.
Please take her back.
I came here to ask you that.
Since Eun Seo was little,
she has been sickly and fragile.
So I have been taking care of her
very delicately.
Eun Seo is my daughter.
Please let me raise her.
Don't you feel sorry for Sin Ae that
could not enjoy nice meals and clothes...
growing up in this house?
Take good care of her.
I cannot take care of Sin Ae well.
My husband's gambling and illness...
took up all the money in the house.
I have done all kinds of jobs
to make ends meet.
Surviving was my top priority,
so I could not take care of her well.
That is probably why Sin Ae...
has not been a nice and kind girl.
Take good care of her.
Although
I could not take care of her well,
Sin Ae is my only daughter.
I cannot send her away.
I wanted to tell you to let us live
as we did.
What has Sin Ae been like?
Has she been eating well?
She has.
When did she say her first words?
When did she start to walk?
I am sorry.
Sin Ae, was she pretty
even when she was little?
Did she have a lot of friends?
Sin Ae.
My Sin Ae
Please take good care of her.
Take good care of her.
My pale pink skirt is
Fluttering
In the spring wind
Biting my dress string again today
On the village shrine road
visited by spring maidens
When the flowers bloom
We laugh together
When the flowers fall
We cry together
With that sweet vow
Spring days are gone
Yoon Eun Seo.
Choi Sin Ae, what is it?
Where are you going?
I'm going home.
That is not the way to your home.
What are you talking about?
Yoon Eun Seo.
No, Choi Eun Seo.
Are you scared?
Are you scared that the soup lady
became your mom all of a sudden?
Are you scared
you will have a gangster brother?
You are bad. You are so mean.
She is your mother.
How could you say that
about the lady who raised you?
You are so mean.
- Choi Sin Ae.
- Let's go together.
What do you know?
What do you know about my family
to tell me I'm mean?
Let's go. See it yourself.
Choi Sin Ae. What are you doing?
You stay out of it.
Come with me.
Eun Seo.
What should I do?
Jun Seo, there is a problem.
Sin Ae took Eun Seo to her house.
- What?
- Jun Seo, hurry.
Soon Im.
Hard times for you are over now.
I heard Sin Ae's biological parents
are really wealthy.
Where did you hear that?
The whole school knows about it.
My child told me.
So, how much are you getting?
Take as much as you want.
You have raised their child for 14 years.
They mustn't pretend that was nothing.
Don't you think so?
- Get out of here.
- What are you...?
Are you going crazy
because you're so excited?
Get out of my face.
Do you always think about
how to make money by using your children?
How dare you say that?
What?
You!
Sin Ae.
I am not Sin Ae. She is.
Sin Ae, you idiot.
She is your daughter.
Jun Seo.
Sin...
Let's go.
What are you doing? Let's go home.
Sin Ae.
Jun Seo hit me.
Because of Eun Seo.
Because of her.
A girl should not wander around crying.
Dinner is ready, so wash your hands.
- Honey.
- I will go.
I can leave.
You live with Eun Seo.
Why do you hate me so much?
Why do you hate me?
I am your daughter. You are my mom.
I do errands for drinkers
at the restaurant every day.
My mom always works,
and my brother hits me.
Like Eun Seo, I want pretty clothes...
and affection from my brother.
Can't I have that?
Don't I deserve to be loved
by Mom and Dad?
Is it bad I am asking for those?
Am I asking for too much
that you would hate me like this?
You are my biological mother.
My real mom.
Mom.
Sin Ae, I am sorry.
I am so sorry.
Sin Ae, don't cry.
Don't cry, Sin Ae. I am sorry.
I am so sorry.
Don't cry, Sin Ae.
- We are back.
- Jun Seo.
Jun Seo, come with me.
- Later.
- What?
Dad, Jun Seo is...
Why did you hit your sister?
I did not hit Eun Seo.
I did not hit my sister.
It would be very uncomfortable for Sin Ae
with this sudden change.
You and Eun Seo should look after her.
Sin Ae is also your sister.
She is not my sister.
My sister is here.
After all this time...
She might mean a lot to you and Mom,
but not to me.
Tell her to go back to her house.
Dad.
Jun Seo.
You go inside.
What about Eun Seo?
Do you even care about Eun Seo?
Don't cry.
Don't cry, Mom.
Eun Seo, you have grown up.
You can even get married.
I agree.
Eun Seo, my Eun Seo.
The most beautiful daughter in the world.
My daughter, Eun Seo.
Eun Seo is not pretty at all. She is ugly.
Dad, Mom, and Jun Seo.
Thank you all.
Thank you for raising me
and taking care of me so far.
I will take them with me.
Then, I will be with you always.
Dad, goodbye.
Mom, the one I love the most. Bye.
And...
Jun Seo, goodbye.
Eun Seo.
Yoon Eun Seo.
Eun Seo!
Stop there.
Leave the money.
It is also Eun Seo's birthday today.
Please give me Eun Seo back.
Please let me meet Eun Seo.
Mom.
I can't go with you.
Eun Seo.
Eun Seo. No.
What do you want to be
if you were to be born again?
What about you?
I want to be a tree.
Once it has taken root,
it can't move anywhere else.
I want to be such a tree.
Then I won't have to part with
anyone ever again.
Jun Seo,
what is the name of your first love?
Tree.